Guide to the Rice University Information Files, 1910-2019 UA 361
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series XIX: S
  - Students - Blind
  - Students - Exchange and Study Abroad
  - Students - Foreign
  - Students - Minorities
    See also: Johnson, Raymond Lewis
  - Students For A Democratic Society
  - Studies in English Literature (SEL)
  - Studio X
  - [The] Study Lounge
  - Study Abroad
  - Sugar Bowl
  - Suicides
  - Sullender Maurice ('41) & Maureen Martin ('39)
  - Sullivan, Louis W.
  - Suman, Don
  - Suman, John R.
  - Summer Program
  - Summer School Enrichment Program
  - Summer School for High School Students
  - Summit of the Minds
  - Sun, Y. Ping (Mrs. David Leebron)
  - [1974] Super Bowl at Rice Stadium
  - Super Computer, 2002
  - Surls, James 2010
  - Sustainability Planning/Project
  - Sutton, Steve
  - Svedberg, Dr. The
    See also: Anderson, Dr. Carl D.
  - Swift, Stephen K.
  - Swimming
  - Switzer, Warren
  - Symonds, H. Gardiner
  - [Henry Gardiner] Symonds Professorship
  - [Henry Gardiner] Symonds Teaching Lab
  - [Rice] Symphonic Society
  - Syzygysts
- Series XX: T
  - "Table Talk"
  - Tablets to Arts and Sciences
  - Taft, William Howard
  - Tagore, Rabindranath
  - Talbot, Raymond J.
  - Talmage, Roy V.
  - The Talon
  - Talwani, Manik
  - Taner, M. Turhan
  - Taniguchi, Alan Y.
  - Tanlac
  - Tao, Jane
  - "Tape"
  - Tapia, Richard
  - Tarlov, Alvin
  - Task Force on Slavery, Segregation, and Racial Injustice
  - Tattlers Club
  - Tau Beta Pi
  - Taylor, Julie
  - Taylor, William
  - Teach for America
  - [Rice] Teacher Education Council
  - Teaching Awards - Amoco
  - Teaching Awards - George R. Brown
  - Teaching Awards - Phi Beta Kappa outstanding teaching of an assistant professor
  - Teaching Awards - Salgo award for teaching excellence
  - Teague, James U.
  - Teas, Edward
  - Tea-Trike Race
  - Technical Writers and Publishers, Society of
  - Technology Transfer Office
  - [El] Tecolote
  - Teich, Frank
    See also: Glenwood Cemetary
  - [Rice] Television Programs
  - Teller, Edward
  - Temkin, Larry S.
  - ten Birnk, Dr. Karl C.
  - Tennis
  - Tennis, 1913/14 - 1938/39
  - Tennis, 1939/40 - 1977/78
  - Tennis, 1980's - current
  - [George R. Brown] Tennis Center
  - Tennis Scrapbook, 1929/30
  - Tennis Tournaments
  - Tenure
  - Ten Year Plan at Rice
  - Teutonic Production
  - Texas A & M
  - Texas Academy of Science
  - Texas Africa Business Summit
  - Texas Bowl 2008
  - Texas Digital Library
  - Texas Environmental Library and Resource Center
  - Texas Environmental Survey 1990-92
  - Texas Instruments
  - Texas Intercollegiate Student Association
  - Texas Library Association
  - Texas Medical Center
  - Texas Philosophical Society
  - Texas Salon
  - Texas School of Civics and Philanthropy
  - Texas Southern University - Rice University Dual Degree Program
  - Texas-UK Collaborative
  - TexPirg
  - Thacker, Allison
  - Thalian Club
  - Thanksgiving Day Reunion, 1919
  - Thanksgiving Day Service 1953/54
  - [Rice College] Theater
  - "The Other Rice News"
  - Theft
  - Thierstein, Joel
  - Thom, William T., Jr.
  - Thomas, Albert
  - [Albert] Thomas Chair in Political Science
  - [Albert] Thomas Dinner, 1961
    See also: Thomas, Albert
  - Thomas, Edwin "Ned"
  - Thomas, Joe D.
  - Thompson, Ewa M.
  - Thompson, Howard A.
  - Thompson, James R.
  - Thompson, Scott
  - Thomson, Sir George
  - Thomson, T.A., Jr.
  - Thorp, Willard
  - Thornton, Patrick
  - Thrall, Robert M.
  - Thrane, Linda
  - [Rice] Thrasher
  - [Rice] Thresher (2 folders)
  - Throckmorton, Chuck
  - Tidden, John C.
  - Tile Work [on Original Campus Buildings]
  - Tillich, Paul
  - [Rice] Timberland
  - Tippett, Giles
  - Tipton, Albert
  - Tipton, Mary N.
  - Tittel, Frank
  - Tobacco Investment Stock
  - Tobin, Mary Lampland
  - Todd, Anderson
  - Todd, Emily
  - Tomson, Mason
  - Topazio, Virgil
  - Torczon, Linda
  - Torrens, Mrs. W.B.
  - Touchdown Club of Houston
  - Tour, Jim
  - Toynbee, Arnold
  - Track, 1913/14 - 1921/22
  - Track, 1922/23 - 1931/32
  - Track, 1932/33 - 1936/37
  - Track, 1937/38 - 1938/39
  - Track, 1939/40 - 1941/42
  - Track, 1942/43 - 1946/47, 50s
  - Track, 1965/66 - 1971/72
  - Track, 1977/78 - 1979
  - Track, 1980's - 1990's - 2000's
  - Track and Field, 1920's - 1930's
  - Track and Field, 1980's - current
  - Trademarks
  - Traffic and Parking Regulations
  - Trammell, George T.
  - Trammell, Mary
  - Transnational China Project
  - "Trasher"
    See also: "Space City"; "Thrasher"
  - Traveling Salesman Problem
  - Traweek, Sharon
  - Treasurers
  - Tree Campus, USA
  - [Rice] Trees
    See also: Landscaping
  - Trepel, Shirley
  - Trinity College (Cambridge) - Rice Exchange
  - [Rice] Trivia
  - Troelstra, Arne
  - Trolley
  - [Rice] Trophy Case
  - Tropical Storm Imelda
  - Trotter, Jack T.
  - Truscott, Bob
  - "The Trust" (film)
  - Tsanoff Chair of Public Affairs
  - Tsanoff Endowment Fund
  - Tsanoff, Radoslav A.
  - Tudor, Bobby
  - Tudor, Bobby and Phoebe
  - Tudor Fieldhouse
  - Tuggle, Francis D.
  - Tug o' War
  - Tuition
  - Tuition Equalization Grant (TEG)
  - Tuna Fest
  - [Rice] Tunnels
  - Turnbull, Pender
  - Turner, Drexel
  - [Isla and Percy] Turner Professorship in Biblical Studies
  - Turner, Richard B.
  - [James] Turrell Skyspace
  - Tutoring Project
  - Twinkies
  - [William G.] Twyman Chair in History
  - Tyler, Stephen A.
  - Tyrrell, John F.
  - Tyson, Rev. Brady
- Series XXI: U
  - Udden, Rebecca Greene
  - UFO
  - Umstattd, James Greenleaf
  - Unconvention, April 12-14, 2012
  - "Unconventional Wisdom"
  - Undergraduate Research
  - Underground at Lovett
  - Underhill, Michael
  - Underwood, Wash
  - Underwood, Milton R.
  - Unemployment Workshop
  - United Behavioral Health (formerly Employee Assistance Program)
  - United Nation's Council of Houston
  - [Rice] United Way News
  - University Blue, The
  - University Council
    See also: [Rice] Faculty Gov. and Part.
  - [Rice] University Court
  - University Extension Lectures
  - University of Houston
  - University of St. Thomas
  - University Support Staff (USS) (employee organization)
  - Upper Atmosphere Research corporation
  - Urban League Scholarship Program (with Rice University, 1999)
  - Urban Research Center
    See also: Kinder Institute for Urban Research
  - Urban Research, Southwest Center for (SCUR)
  - Urbish, Leona
  - Ushinsky, Constantin D.
  - USS Houston
  - USS Texas
- Series XXII: V
  - V-12 Program
  - Vail, Peter R.
  - Valdivieso, Mercedes (Mercedes Callahan)
  - Valenzuela, Angela
  - Valhalla
  - Valkovic, Vlado
  - Valley, John W.
  - Van Allen, James A.
  - Van Buren, Richard
  - Van de Graaff Accelerator
  - Vanden Heuvel, William J.
    See also: Lectures - President's Series
  - Vander Henst, J.F.
  - Vandiver, Frank E.
  - Vandiver, Susan
  - Van Dyke, Henry
  - Van Helden, Albert
  - Van Sicklen, W.J.
  - Van Slyke, Glen
  - Van Wambeck, S.H.
  - Vanzant, Frances
  - Vardi, Moshe
  - Veech, William A.
  - Veggie Club
  - Veletsos, A.S.
  - Velz, John W.
  - Verheyden, Jack C.
  - Vernon, Clayton
  - Veruki, Peter E.
  - Veterans Day
  - [Rice] Veterans of Future Wars
  - Vietnam War Moratorium
    See also: Student Protests
  - Vietti, Teresa J.
  - Village Arcade
  - Village Theater
  - Viner, Jacob
  - Vision for Rice's 2nd Century
  - Vision Program
  - Vision Weekend
  - Visitors Center
  - Visitors Guide
  - Visual and Dramatic Arts, Dept. of
    See also: Art and Art History, Department of
  - Volleyball
  - Volterra, Vito
  - Von der Mehden, Fred
  - Von Johnson, George S.
  - Von Johnson, Kurt
  - Vonnegut, Kurt
  - Von Weizsacker, Dr. C. F.
  - Von Weizsacker, Richard
  - Voswinkel, Mary
  - [The] Vox
    See also: Rice Republicans
- Series XXIII: W
  - Wadsworth, P.A.
  - Waggaman, Adele
  - Waggaman, Camille
  - Wagner, Brock
  - Waldo, Wilmer
  - Walker, Curtis Howe
  - Walker, James B.
  - Walker, William F.
  - Wall, Frederick T.
  - Wallace, Bill
  - Wallace, Kristine Gilmartin
    See also: Gilmartin, Kristine
  - Wallach, Dan
  - Walters, G. King
  - Walters, Henry
  - Walters, Tyler
  - Wamble, Mark
  - Wang, Chao-Cheng
  - Wann, Trenton W.
  - Waples, Rachel
  - War Training Courses
  - Ward, Calvin H.
    See also: Groundwater Research Center
  - Ward, Charles Frederick
  - Ward, Herb
  - Ward, Joseph Anthony
  - Ward, Roy
  - Ware, Dr. Stacy
  - War Games and Role Playing Club of Rice University
  - Warme, John E.
  - Warren, Joe
  - Washington Cemetery
  - [Rice] Water Polo
  - Water Well
  - Waters, James S.
  - Watkin, William Ward
  - [William Ward] Watkin Fellowship
  - Watkins, Joel S.
  - Watkins, Michael J.
  - Watson Fellowship
  - [Thomas J.] Watson Foundation
  - Watson, Keith
  - Watts, André
  - Weaver, Ralph
  - Weber, Rolf Felix
  - Web Week
  - Webb, George W. III
  - [F. Carrington] Weems Family
  - Weinberg, Alvin M.
  - Weingarten, Joe
    See also: World Institute for World Peace
  - Weingarten Professor of International Relations
  - Weiser, Harry B.
  - Weisman, Bruce R.
  - Weissenberger, Klaus
  - [Robert A.] Welch Chair in Chemistry
  - Welch Foundation
  - Welch, Robert A.
  - [Rice] Welcome Center
  - Wellbeing Office
  - Wellness Center
  - Wells, Damon
  - Wells, Raymond O., Jr.
  - Welsh, Hugh
  - Weltsch, Ruben
  - Wendt, Gerald L.
  - West, Jennifer
  - [James Murion] West Mansion
    See also: NASA; Lunar Science Institute; Johnson Space Center
  - West University Place
    See also: Neighborhoods (near Rice)
  - Westbrook, Robert
  - Western Athletic Conference
  - Westheimer, David
  - Westmeyer, R.E.
  - Wheel of Fortune (TV game show)
  - Wheeler, Mary
  - Whitaker Foundation Graduate Fellowships
  - Whitaker, Gilbert R., Jr.
  - White, Bill (Houston, Mayor)
  - White, James Francis Collection
  - White, Kenneth J.
  - Whiting, Sarah
  - Whitmire, Kathy
  - Whitmire, Kenneth
  - Whitmore, Bill
  - Whitmore, Frank Clifford
  - Whitson, Peggy
  - Whittington, Harmon
  - "Who Knew?" Campaign
  - Who's Who Among American Universities and Colleges
  - Widrig, Walter M.
  - Wiener, Martin J.
  - Wierum, Frederic
  - Wiesner, Mark R.
  - [Harry C.] Wiess Chair in Geology
  - Wiess, Harry Carothers
  - Wiess, Olga Keith
  - Wiess Residence - Shadyside
    See also: President's House
  - Wiess School of Natural Sciences
  - Wihl, Gary S.
  - Will, George
  - Willcot, Bob
  - William Marsh Rice Society
  - Williams, Donald
  - Williams, Edward
  - Williams, George
  - Williams, George - Celebration, October 23, 1992
  - Williams, Greg
  - Williams, James A. "Froggy"
  - Williams, Linda Faye
  - Williams, Linda Faye Social Justice Prize
    See also: Williams, Linda Faye
  - Williams, Robert
  - Williams, Willoughby C.
  - Williamson, James G.
  - Wilson, Bill (William L.)
  - Wilson, Cynthia
  - Wilson, Ellen Axson (Mrs. Woodrow)
  - Wilson, F. Talbot
  - Wilson Fellowship
  - Wilson, Lord Harold (British PM)
  - Wilson, Harold Albert
  - Wilson, James L.
  - Wilson, Joseph
  - Wilson, Lon J.
  - Wilson, Rick
  - Wilson, Robert W.
  - Wilson, Thomas Redyard
  - Wilson, Willis
  - Wilson, Woodrow
  - Wincenc, Carol
  - Windsor, Duane
  - Wingenroth, Kris
  - Wingfield, B. Magruder
  - Winkler, Kathy
  - Winkler, Michael
  - Winningham, Geoff
  - Winston, James O., Jr.
  - Winston, Leland
  - Wischmeyer, Carl R.
  - Wise, Scott
  - Witlington, Harmon
  - Witt, Harry
  - Wittenberg, Gordon
  - Wittung-Stafshede, Pernilla
  - Wojecki, Eddie
  - Wolf, Michael
  - Wolf, Richard A
  - Wolfe, Cary
  - Wolfe, Joel
  - Wolin, Richard
  - Wolynes, Peter
  - Women [at Rice]
  - Women Engineers
  - [Rice] Women's Commission
  - [Rice] Women's Conference
  - Women's Council
  - Women's History Conference
  - [Rice] Women's Housing
  - Women's Institute
  - Women's Interest Network
  - [Rice U.] Women's Resource Center
  - [Rice] Women's Studies
  - Wong, Michael
  - Wood, Sharolyn
  - Wood, Susan
  - Woodburn, James
  - Woodson, Benjamin N.
  - Woodson Research Center
  - Woodward, Clare
  - Wooldridge, Bonnie Sue
  - Worden, Sam P. & Helen Saba
  - Wordsworthless Society
  - World Energy Congress International Student Program
  - World Institute for World Peace
  - World War I
  - World War I + II Correspondence from Rice Students
  - World War II - Registration, Newsclips
    See also: scrapbooks
  - Wortham, Gus
  - Wortham Professorship of Architecture
  - Worthing Rice Apprenticeship Program
  - Wright, Ann
  - [Rice] Writers' Conference
  - Writing Across the Curriculum Conference
  - Writing Center
  - Wu, Harry
  - Wyschogrod, Edith
- Series XXIV: X
  - Xu, Qianfan
- Series XXV: Y
  - Y2K
  - Yakobson, Boris
  - Yamal, Ricardo
  - Yankee Stadium
  - Yarborough, Ralph
  - Ye Olde College Inn
  - Yeager, Donna
  - Yeager, John
  - Yekovich, Robert
  - Yerges, Marjorie North
    1923 Photo
  - Yew, Lee Kuan
  - YMCA
  - Young Alumni Business Network Association
  - Young Democrat Club
  - Young Republican Club
  - Young, Richard Donald
  - Yunis, Harvey E.
- Series XXVI: Z
  - Zammito, John
  - Zander, Whitlock Jr.
  - [Hotel] ZaZa
  - Zansitis, Richard A.
  - Zdatny, Steven M.
  - Zeff, Steven A.
  - Zeidenstein, Darrow
  - Zelt, Colin
  - Zerow House
  - Zimmerman, Thomas
  - Zipcar
  - Zodrow, George
  - [Houston] Zoo
  - Zubarev, Eugene
  - Zygourakis, Kiriacos